questions =[{
                "Question": "1. India is a federal union comprising twenty-nine states and how many union territories?",
                "a": "6",
                "b": "7",
                "c": "8",
                "d": "9",
                "ans": "ans4",
            }, {
                "Question": "2. Which of the following is the capital of Arunachal Pradesh?",
                "a": "Itanagar",
                "b": "Dispur",
                "c": "Imphal",
                "d": "Panaji",
                "ans": "ans1",
            },{
                "Question": "3. What are the major languages spoken in Andhra Pradesh?",
                "a": "English and Telugu",
                "b": "Telugu and Urdu",
                "c": "Telugu and Kannada",
                "d": "All of the above languages",
                "ans": "ans2",
            },{
                "Question": "4. What is the state flower of Haryana?",
                "a": "Lotus",
                "b": "Rhododendron",
                "c": "Golden Shower",
                "d": "Not declared",
                "ans": "ans1",
            }, {
                "Question": "5. Which of the following states is not located in the North?",
                "a": "Jharkhand",
                "b": "Jammu and Kashmir",
                "c": "Himachal Pradesh",
                "d": "Haryana",
                "ans": "ans1",
            }, {
                "Question": "6. In which state is the main language Khasi?",
                "a": "Mizoram",
                "b": "Nagaland",
                "c": "Meghalaya",
                "d": "Tripura",
                "ans": "ans3",
            }, {
                "Question": "7. Which is the largest coffee producing state of India?",
                "a": "Kerala",
                "b": "Tamil Nadu",
                "c": "Karnataka",
                "d": "Arunachal Pradesh",
                "ans": "ans3",
            }, {
                "Question": "8. Which state has the largest area?",
                "a": "Maharashtra",
                "b": "Madhya Pradesh",
                "c": "Uttar Pradesh",
                "d": "Rajasthan",
                "ans": "ans4",
            }, {
                "Question": "9. Which state has the largest population?",
                "a": "Uttar Pradesh",
                "b": "Maharastra",
                "c": "Bihar",
                "d": "West Bengal",
                "ans": "ans1",
            }, {
                "Question": "10. In what state is the Elephant Falls located?",
                "a": "Mizoram",
                "b": "Orissa",
                "c": "Manipur",
                "d": "Meghalaya",
                "ans": "ans4",
            }, {
                "Question": "1. India is a federal union comprising twenty-nine states and how many union territories?",
                "a": "6",
                "b": "7",
                "c": "8",
                "d": "9",
                "ans": "ans4",
            }, ]